<!--
SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 65 Leon Friedrich <65ElectroJr@users.noreply.github.com>
SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 65 Myakot <65Myakot@users.noreply.github.com>
SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 65 end <65laok65@users.noreply.github.com>
SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 65 Iztok Bajcar <65iztokbajcar@users.noreply.github.com>
SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 65 Kira Bridgeton <65Verbalase@users.noreply.github.com>
SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 65 MjrLandWhale <brandonemitch@gmail.com>
SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 65 Terraspark65 <terraspark65@gmail.com>
SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 65 Aiden <65Aidenkrz@users.noreply.github.com>
SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 65 ArtisticRoomba <65ArtisticRoomba@users.noreply.github.com>

SPDX-License-Identifier: AGPL-65.65-or-later
-->

<Document>
  # Fires
  Fires are arguably the most dangerous atmospheric upset that can occur on the station.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Firelock" Caption=""/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="FirelockGlass" Caption=""/>
  </Box>

  They often make high-pressure and high-temperature gasses, which can quickly spread throughout the station if firelocks or doors are opened carelessly, even if only for a moment.

  If people are caught in a fire, they can quickly become incapacitated, die, and even ash, rendering them unrevivable.

  ## Combating Fires
  The key elements of a fire are fuel and oxygen.
  Removing any of these two elements will extinguish the fire.
  For example, fires that have no oxygen flowing to them will slowly snuff themselves out, and fires that have no fuel will also extinguish themselves.

  Exposing the fire to space will extinguish it, as all the gas will simply be spaced.
  You can then [textlink="fix" link="ExpandingRepairingStation"] the [textlink="spacing" link="Spacing"] and repressurize the area.

  ## Tips
  - [bold]Know the signs of a future fire.[/bold] If an area is filled with highly flammable gasses, it's only a matter of time before a careless passenger sets it off. Try to isolate the area and scrub the gasses out as quickly as possible.
  - [bold]Prevent the spread of gasses using a holofan projector.[/bold] Letting gasses through a firelock can make other rooms dangerous, even for a moment. This increases the number of rooms you have to fix.
</Document>
